sugoitw.com 2011-06-09

# 8dimentions.com Privacy Policy | taiwanese idol drama online fast streaming with english subtitles and full version high quality download - tw.sugoitw.com

(last update: Apr 2009)

At tw.sugoitw.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by tw.sugoitw.com.com and how it is used.

The following information is gathered from our website visitors: IP address

**How we use the information we gather**

Like most standard Web site servers, tw.sugoitw.com.com use log files. This includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, browser type, internet service provider ( ISP ), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
We use the information to enhance your visitor experience.

**Our use of cookies**

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.  
Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
